Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- Errata in Rogers' AGC Catalogue, 1904; KG11366.804 (Box 75)
- Meridian Circle - General Record, 1879 to 1880; KG11366.805 (Box 76)
- Constellations, KG11366.806 (Box 76)
- Working List of Star Data, 1871; KG11366.807 (Box 76)
- Working List of Star Data for 1880, 1880 to 1881; KG11366.808 (Box 76)
- Constellation Data, 1879 to 1880; KG11366.809 (Box 76)
- Reduction of Bonn Observations from 1855 to 1875, KG11366.810 (Box 76)
- Discordant Stars, KG11366.811 (Box 76)
- Reports on Obsn of Stars in N. Hemisphere on 9th May, Pulkovo, 1879; KG11366.812 (Box 76)
- Star Reduction, 1890; KG11366.813 (Box 76)
- Measure of Plates, 1890; KG11366.814 (Box 76)
- Computations - Longitude and Latitude of Bolivian and Peruvian Stations, no. 2, 1894; KG11366.815 (Box 76)
- Zone Observations, 1883 to 1884; KG11366.816 (Box 76)
- Measurements, Micrometer, no. 1, 1894 to 1897; KG11366.817 (Box 76)
- Sun Images, 1880; KG11366.818 (Box 76)
- Miscellaneous Notes, KG11366.819 (Box 76)
  D.C. Bard.
- Chronograph Sheet readings, 1884; KG11366.820 (Box 76)
- Computation of Residuals, KG11366.821 (Box 76)
- Correction for Error, 1869 to 1870; KG11366.822 (Box 76)
- Observation of Southern Variable Stars, 1899 to 1904; KG11366.823 (Box 76)
- Nautical Almanac, 1883; KG11366.824 (Box 76)
- Lunar Brightness, 1881; KG11366.825 (Box 76)
- 12-inch Horizontal Telescope Records, XII., 1899; KG11366.826 (Box 77)
- Satellite IV, 1888 to 1890; KG11366.827 (Box 77)
- Reductions, KG11366.828 (Box 77)
- Bibliography, KG11366.829 (Box 77)
- Observations and Reductions Part II, 1876; KG11366.830 (Box 77)
- Observations and Reductions Part III, 1876; KG11366.831 (Box 77)
- Re-readings of Chronograph Sheets, 1880; KG11366.832 (Box 77)
- Investigations of Division Errors of Circle East, 1880 to 1881; KG11366.833 (Box 77)
- Chronograph Readings, 1881; KG11366.834 (Box 77)
  H. Stevens.
- Readings of Chronograph Sheets, 1879; KG11366.835 (Box 77)
- Star Data, 1884 to 1885; KG11366.836 (Box 77)
- Star Data, 1882; KG11366.837 (Box 77)
- Star and Comet Data, 1881 to 1884; KG11366.838 (Box 77)
  P.C. Ricketts.
- Reductions, 1880 to 1881; KG11366.839 (Box 77)
- Comet Data and Comparison Stars, 1881; KG11366.840 (Box 77)
- Time Service, 1885 to 1886; KG11366.841 (Box 77)
- Dates of Observations of Zone Stars for 1883 and 1884, KG11366.842 (Box 77)
- Miscellaneous Star Observations, KG11366.843 (Box 77)
- Star Observations, KG11366.844 (Box 77)
- Zone Observations, 1884; KG11366.845 (Box 77)
- Fundamental Zone Star Circle Readings, 1885; KG11366.846 (Box 77)
- Current Observations of Variable Stars, 1895 to 1896; KG11366.847 (Box 78)
- Record of Observations, 1898 to 1899; KG11366.848 (Box 78)
  F.W. Grover.
- Variable Star Observations, 1899 to 1900; KG11366.849 (Box 78)
  H.C. Bailey.
- Absolute Work Runs 1879, 80, 81, 1898 to 1899; KG11366.850 (Box 78)
- [Variable Stars], 1883 to 1884; KG11366.851 (Box 78)
- West Dome 6.25-inch, 1883; KG11366.852 (Box 78)
- West Dome 6.25-inch, 1883; KG11366.853 (Box 78)
- West Dome 6.25-inch, 1896 to 1898; KG11366.854 (Box 78)
- Wedge Zones, 1887; KG11366.855 (Box 78)
- Correction to Ephemerides - Jupiter's Satellites, KG11366.856 (Box 78)
- Final Adopted Magnitudes: Comp Stars for Variables, 1901; KG11366.857 (Box 78)
- Final Adopted Magnitudes: Comp Stars for Variables, 1900; KG11366.858 (Box 78)
- Variable and Other Stars, 1889 to 1890; KG11366.859 (Box 78)
- Variable Star Observations, 1894 to 1895; KG11366.860 (Box 78)
- Variable Stars, 1898 to 1899; KG11366.861 (Box 78)
- Computation Book, 1899 to 1900; KG11366.862 (Box 78)
- Computation Book, 1902; KG11366.863 (Box 78)
- Wedge Photometer Zone Stars, 1894; KG11366.864 (Box 78)
- Meridian Photometry, 1881 to 1884; KG11366.865 (Box 78)
- Multiplet Theory (N.N. Russel) - Notes, 1925; KG11366.866 (Box 78)
- Plates to be Examined re. Peters' Zones, 1877 to 1878; KG11366.867 (Box 79)
- Equatorial Zones, 1877; KG11366.868 (Box 79)
  Also identified as: R21.
- Location of Comparison Stars for Variables, 1894; KG11366.869 (Box 79)
- Crown Flint Optical Data, 1902 to 1903; KG11366.870 (Box 79)
- Chronograph Record, 1870; KG11366.871 (Box 79)
- Chronograph Record, 1870 to 1871; KG11366.872 (Box 79)
- Chronometer comparisons, 1896 to 1897; KG11366.873 (Box 79)
  R.D. Ward.
- Miscellaneous Notes and Work Plans, 1862 to 1869; KG11366.874 (Box 79)
- Variable Star Observations, 1901; KG11366.875 (Box 79)
  See also KG11365.778.
- Thermometer Readings, KG11366.876 (Box 79)
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.877 (Box 79)
  Mary Fowler.
  862, 872, 873.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.878 (Box 79)
  864, 865, 878, 879.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.879 (Box 79)
  920, 921, 922, 932.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.880 (Box 79)
  933, 934, 966, 967.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.881 (Box 79)
  968, 972, 974, 977.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.882 (Box 79)
  978, 979, 1028, 1029.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.883 (Box 79)
  1030, 1034, 1035, 1049.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.884 (Box 79)
  1050, 1051, 1067, 1068, 1069.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.885 (Box 79)
  1041, 1042, 1043, 1078, 1079.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.886 (Box 79)
  1080, 1085, 1086, 1122, 1092.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.887 (Box 79)
  1093, 1094, 1123, 1124, 1125.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.888 (Box 79)
  1126, 1128.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.889 (Box 79)
  1129, 1130.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.890 (Box 79)
  Also identified as: Vol. 15 [sic].
  1301, 1302, 1303.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.891 (Box 79)
  1166, 1257.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.892 (Box 79)
  1304, 1305.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.893 (Box 79)
  Also identified as: Vol. 17.
  1307, 1308, 1309.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.894 (Box 79)
  1310, 1311, 1312.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.895 (Box 79)
  1313, 1314, 1315.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.896 (Box 79)
  1318, 1319, 1331.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.897 (Box 79)
  1168.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.898 (Box 79)
  1332, 1375, 1376.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.899 (Box 80)
  1380, 1381, 1397.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.900 (Box 80)
  1398, 1402, 1403.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.901 (Box 80)
  1407, 1408, 1412.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.902 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 26.
  1413, 1446, 1445.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.903 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 27.
  1452, 1453, 1462.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.904 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 28.
  1463, 1518, 1519.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.905 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 29.
  1520, 1521, 1524.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.906 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 30.
  1525, 1542, 1543.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.907 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 31.
  1549, 1550, 1590.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.908 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 32.
  1591, 1598.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.909 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 33.
  1599, 1606.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.910 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 34.
  1607, 1662, 1668.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.911 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 35.
  1669, 1674, 1675.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.912 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 36.
  1682, 1683, 1696.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.913 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 37.
  1679, 1702, 1703.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.914 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 38.
  1737, 1739, 1743.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.915 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 39.
  1744, 1747.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.916 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 40.
  1749, 1750, 1751.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.917 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 41.
  1759, 1760, 1790.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.918 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 42.
  1791, 1795.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.919 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 43.
  1796, 1801, 1802.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.920 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 44.
  1808, 1809, 1826.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.921 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 45.
  1827, 1884.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.922 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 46.
  1885, 1889, 1890.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.923 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 47.
  1930, 1931, 1956.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.924 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 48.
  1957, 1963, 1964.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.925 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 49.
  1973, 1974.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.926 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 50.
  1980. 1981, 2009.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.927 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 51.
  2010, 2011, 2012.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.928 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 52.
  2014, 2015, 2074.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.929 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 53.
  2076, 2081, 2082.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.930 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 54.
  2093, 2094, 2145.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.931 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 55.
  2146, 2172.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.932 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 56.
  2173, 2180, 2181.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.933 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 57.
  2184, 2185, 2234.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.934 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 58.
  2235, 2367, 2368.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.935 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 59.
  2374, 2375, 2377.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.936 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 60.
  2378, 2386, 2387.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.937 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 61.
  2493, 2494, 2782.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.938 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 62.
  2783, 2797, 2798.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.939 (Box 80)
  Also identified as: Vol. 63.
  2371, 2182, 2368.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.940 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 64.
  2992, 2994, 3008.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.941 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 65.
  3010, 3023, 3024.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.942 (Box 81)
  1698, 1748.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.943 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 66.
  2751, 2752.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.944 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 67.
  3045, 3046, 3189.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.945 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 68.
  3215, 3376.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.946 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 69.
  3377, 3385, 3384.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.947 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 70.
  3485, 3486, 3535.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.948 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 71.
  3536, 3601.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.949 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 72.
  3648, 3649.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.950 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 73.
  3669, 3783.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.951 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 74.
  3784, 3811.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.952 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 75.
  3812 3844.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.953 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 76.
  3846, 3856.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.954 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 77.
  3857, 4096.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.955 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 78.
  4097, 4239.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.956 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 79.
  4271, 4272.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.957 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 80.
  4295, 4296.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.958 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 81.
  4297, 4298.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.959 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 82.
  4303, 4304, 4309.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.960 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 83.
  4336, 4374, 4375.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.961 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 84.
  4423, 4424, 4455.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.962 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 85.
  4456, 4465, 4466.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.963 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 86.
  4478, 4481.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.964 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 87.
  4503, 4554, 4555.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.965 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 88.
  4571, 4572, 4588.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.966 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 89.
  4589, 4619, 4620.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.967 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 90.
  4677, 4678, 4690.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.968 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 115.
  7549, 7571, 7572. VOL 90-115 absent.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.969 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 116.
  7665, 7666, 7677.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.970 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 117.
  7678, 7692, 7693.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.971 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 118.
  7965, 7966, 7990.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.972 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 119.
  8013, 8014, 8052.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.973 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 120.
  8110, 8288, 8289.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.974 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 121.
  8299, 8300, 8306.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.975 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 122.
  8307, 8316, 8317.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.976 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 123.
  8346, 8347, 8362.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.977 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 124.
  8635, 8636, 8639.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.978 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 125.
  8640, 8904, 8905.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.979 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 126.
  8649, 8650, 8690.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.980 (Box 81)
  Also identified as: Vol. 127.
  8728, 8729.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.981 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 128.
  8726, 8727, 8731.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.982 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 129.
  8732, 8890, 8891.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.983 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 130.
  9079, 9080, 9086.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.984 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 131.
  9087, 9193, 9194.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.985 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 132.
  9195, 9249, 9250.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.986 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 133.
  9263, 9264, 9286.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.987 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 134.
  9377, 9378, 9388.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.988 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 135.
  9389, 9413, 9414.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.989 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 137.
  Ernestine Fuller.
  9461, 9492, 9491..
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.990 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 138.
  9495, 9496, 9732.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.991 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 139.
  9733, 9754, 9782.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.992 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 140.
  9783, 9785, 9786.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.993 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 141.
  9817, 9818, 9859.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.994 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 142.
  9860, 9997, 9998.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.995 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 143.
  10030, 10031, 10072.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.996 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 144.
  10073, 10103, [10102].
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.997 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 145.
  10227, 10228, 10231.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.998 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 146.
  10232, 10263, 10264.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.999 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 147.
  10385, 10386, 10532.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1000 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 148.
  10533, 10604, 10760.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1001 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 149.
  10692, 10693, 10701.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1002 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 150.
  10702, 10716, 10718.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1003 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 151.
  10737, 10738, 10743.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1004 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 152.
  10746, 10748, 10753.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1005 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 153.
  10761, 10933, 10934.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1006 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 154.
  10605, 10998, 10999.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1007 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 155.
  11004, 11006, 11039.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1008 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 156.
  11160, [11161], 11197.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1009 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 157.
  11198, 11201, 11202.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1010 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 158.
  11208, 11209, 11218.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1011 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 159.
  11219, 11276, 11285.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1012 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 160.
  11286, 11301, 11302.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1013 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 161.
  11314, 11315, 11522.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1014 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 162.
  11331, 11336, 11337.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1015 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 163.
  11523, 11542, 11544.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1016 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 164.
  11549, 11550, 11580.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1017 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 165.
  11581, 11597, 11598.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1018 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 166.
  11636, 11708, 11709.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1019 (Box 82)
  Also identified as: Vol. 167.
  11870, 11871, 11890.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1020 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 168.
  11891, 11909, 11910.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1021 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 169.
  11924, 11925, 11931.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1022 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 170.
  11932, 11997, 11998.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1023 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 171.
  12017, 12018, 12027.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1024 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 172.
  12028, 12043, 12044.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1025 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 173.
  12068, 12069, 12075.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1026 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 174.
  12076, 12266, 12267.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1027 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 175.
  12280, 12281, 12296.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1028 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 176.
  12301, 12300, 12297.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1029 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 177.
  12323, 12324, 12469.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1030 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 178.
  12470, 12474, 12475.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1031 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 179.
  12507, 12508, 12525.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1032 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 180.
  12526, 12723, 12724.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1033 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 181.
  12740, 12741, 12774.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1034 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 182.
  12775, 13018, 13019. Missing 11/1991 (?).
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1035 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 184.
  13085, 13274, 13273.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1036 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 185.
  13109, 13110, 13124.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1037 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 186.
  13125, 13143, 13145.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1038 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 187.
  13284, 13285, 13307.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1039 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 188.
  13308, 13329, 13330.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1040 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 189.
  13609, 13611, 13626.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1041 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 190.
  13627, 13641, 13642.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1042 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 191.
  13668, 13669, 13716.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1043 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 192.
  13610, 13645, 13646.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1044 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 193.
  13717, 13935, 13936.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1045 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 194.
  13621, 13622, 13140.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1046 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 195.
  13142.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1047 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 196.
  13331, 13332, 13305.
- Harvard Lunar Plates (Plate Characteristics), KG11366.1048 (Box 83)
  12017-14455.
- Neptune Plates (Princeton), KG11366.1049 (Box 83)
  7099, 7534.
- Neptune Plates (Princeton), KG11366.1050 (Box 83)
- Measures of Lalande 20406, KG11366.1051 (Box 83)
- [Untitled], KG11366.1052 (Box 83)
  4296, 4295.
- Neptune Plates (Princeton), KG11366.1053 (Box 83)
  H.N. Russell.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1054 (Box 83)
  MC650, etc..
- Supplementary Notes and Data, KG11366.1055 (Box 83)
- Hayn's Correction for Plates of Oct. 7, 1911, 1911-10-07; KG11366.1056 (Box 83)
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1057 (Box 83)
  13306, 12319, 12320.
- Neptune Plates (Princeton), KG11366.1058 (Box 83)
- Supplementary Notes, KG11366.1059 (Box 83)
  3535-11998.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1060 (Box 83)
  14455.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1061 (Box 83)
  14448, 14449, 14454.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1062 (Box 83)
  14408, 14416, 14417.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1063 (Box 83)
  14399, 14400, 14407.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1064 (Box 83)
  14095, 14131, 14132.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1065 (Box 83)
  14045, 14046, 14094.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1066 (Box 83)
  13959, 14027, 14028.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1067 (Box 83)
  13914, 13915, 13958.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, KG11366.1068 (Box 83)
  Also identified as: Vol. 136.
  9421, 9422, 9460.
- Fireballs - General Index, KG11366.1069 (Box 84)
  Willard James Fisher.
  Pamphlet Case.
- Correspondence (Lunar Eclipse), KG11366.1070 (Box 85)
- Bright Meteors Reported to HCO 1925-32, KG11366.1071 (Box 86)
- Fireballs, Lunar Eclipse, KG11366.1072 (Box 87)
- Meteors and Fireballs, KG11366.1073 (Box 88)
- Meteors (includes painting), KG11366.1074 (Box 89)
- Meteors, Lunar Eclipse, KG11366.1075 (Box 90)
- Meteors, Fireballs, KG11366.1076 (Box 91)
- Meteors, KG11366.1077 (Box 92)
- Meteors, KG11366.1078 (Box 93)
- Meteors (newspaper clippings), KG11366.1079 (Box 94)
- Observations in 1881ff. - Pickering and Chandler, KG11366.1080 (Box 95)
- Meteor Reports, etc., KG11366.1081 (Box 96)
- Visual observations (Peru), 1894-08-01 to 1896-07-01; KG11367.000 (Box 262)
- Variable Stars in omega Cen, 1898-11-01 to 1898-12-01; KG11367.001 (Box 262)
- Variable Stars in omega Cen, M5, 1899-02-01 to 1901-08-01; KG11367.002 (Box 262)
- Variable Stars in M3, 1900-06-01 to 1901-09-01; KG11367.003 (Box 262)
- [Variable Stars] M3, M5, 1901-12-01 to 1912-09-01; KG11367.004 (Box 262)
- [Variable Stars] NGC 7078, 6656, M22, 1901-07-01 to 1920-10-01; KG11367.005 (Box 262)
  Solon Irving Bailey and Benjamin A. Gould.
  Gould involvement uncertain.
- Miscellaneous Variables and NCG 7078, 6656, M3, M5, 1902-01-01 to 1915-12-01; KG11367.006 (Box 262)
- Variable stars in many clusters, 1922-05-01 to 1923-02-01; KG11367.007 (Box 262)
- Star Counts, Neb. on Map of Sky, LMC, Glob., 1906-03-01 to 1907-01-01; KG11367.008 (Box 262)
- Nebulae, 1907-01-01 to 1908-09-01; KG11367.009 (Box 262)
- Nebulae, 1908-09-01 to 1911-10-01; KG11367.010 (Box 262)
- Positions of Nebulae, vol. 1, 1908-04-01 to 1908-07-01; KG11367.011 (Box 262)
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 3, 1908-09-01 to 1908-10-01; KG11367.012 (Box 262)
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 4, 1908-10-01 to 1908-12-01; KG11367.013 (Box 262)
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 5, 1908-12-01 to 1909-03-01; KG11367.014 (Box 262)